const QUESTIONANSWER = [

	{
		number: 0,
		question: 'Who was the MVP of Super Bowl 1?',
		answers: [
			'Brett Favre',
			'Frank Tarkentin',
			'Bart Starr',
			'John Riggins',
			'Joe Theisman',
		],
		correctAnswer: 2, //'Bart Starr' red flag if coping same info across page
	},

	{
		number: 1,
		question: 'What city hosted the 1980 Summer Olympics?',
		answers: [
			'Moscow, Russia',
			'Atlanta, New York',
			'Mexico City, Mexico',
			'Munich, Germany',
			'Paris, France',
		],
		correctAnswer: 0,
	},
	
	{
		number: 2,
		question: 'Who was the last professional hockey player to play without a helmet?',
		answers: [
			'Bobby Orr',
			'Scott Stevens',
			'Gordie Howe',
			'Bobby Hull',
			'Craig MacTavish',
		],
		correctAnswer: 4,
	},

	{
		number: 3,
		question: 'Grinding is to skateboarding as _______ is to snowboarding.',
		answers: [
			'Hydroplaning',
			'Twerking',
			'Sliding',
			'Jibbing',
			'Railing',
		],
		correctAnswer: 3,
	},

	{
		number: 4,
		question: 'In golf if someone told you the had and albatross today, what do they mean?',
		answers: [
			'They were 3-under par on a single hole.',
			'They were 3-over par on a single hole.',
			'They were 4-under par on a single hole.',
			'They were 4-over par on a single hole.',
			'They were 2-under par on a single hole.',
		],
		correctAnswer: 0,
	},

	{
		number: 5,
		question: 'In the MLB, what phrase became famous in the Barry Bonds steroid case?',
		answers: [
			'Andro and Test',
			'D-Bol and the Clear',
			'The Cream and Tren',
			'The Cream and the Clear',
			'HGH and Protein Shakes',
		],
		correctAnswer: 3,
	},

	{
		number: 6,
		question: 'What Nascar race is known as the \'Super Bowl of Racing\'?',
		answers: [
			'Southern 500 at Darlington',
			'Coca-Cola 600 at Charlotte',
			'Daytona 500',
			'Brickyard 400 at Indianapolis',
			'Championship Race at Homestead',
		],
		correctAnswer: 2,
	},

	{
		number: 7,
		question: 'What are the \'Big 3\' in powerlifting?',
		answers: [
			'Bench press, Deadlift, Squat',
			'Bench press, Curls, Squat',
			'Curls, Lunges, Pull-Ups',
			'Squat, Deadlift, Rows',
			'Pull-Ups, Squat, Push-Ups',
		],
		correctAnswer: 0,
	},

	{
		number: 8,
		question: 'In Bowling what is the term used when a player bowls 3 strikes in a row?',
		answers: [
			'Chicken',
			'Turkey',
			'Horse',
			'Rooster',
			'Eagle',
		],
		correctAnswer: 1,
	},

	{
		number: 9,
		question: 'Tom Brady, Michael Jordan, and Wayne Gretzky are also know as the _______ in their respective sport.',
		answers: [
			'DOG',
			'GOLD',
			'LVP',
			'BOAT',
			'GOAT',	
		],
		correctAnswer: 4,
	},
];
